Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Katherine and today we're talking about one of our favorite topics here at EnglishPod
我是Katherine，今天我们要聊的是我们在EnglishPod最喜欢的话题之一。
that would be food.
那就是食物。
We love talking about food and this time we are going to pick up some food at the deli.
我们喜欢谈论食物，这次我们要去熟食店买些吃的。
What's a deli?
什么是熟食店？
A deli is a special store where a person can buy meat.
熟食店是一种特殊的商店，人们可以在那里买肉。
Meat and cheese and in this case we're talking about special meats.
肉和奶酪，而这次我们说的是特制肉类。
It's not just like pork or beef which you could also buy at the butcher.
它不像猪肉或牛肉那样，你也能在肉铺买到。
It is cured meats, cold meats.
它是腌制肉、冷切肉。
So let's take a look at today's vocabulary preview to find out more about this special
那么，让我们看看今天的词汇预览，了解更多关于这种特制
kind of meat.
肉类。
Vocabulary Preview.
词汇预览。
Alright so at the deli you usually pick up cold cuts.
好的，在熟食店你通常会买冷切肉。
Cold cuts.
冷切肉。
So basically the way that I used to remember cold cuts as a child was that cold cuts are
基本上，我小时候记住冷切肉的方式是，冷切肉就是
what you put on a sandwich.
你放在三明治上的东西。
So sliced turkey, sliced chicken, ham, salami.
比如切片火鸡、切片鸡肉、火腿、萨拉米香肠。
Okay like pepperoni would be a cold cut.
对，像意大利辣香肠就是一种冷切肉。
That's right.
没错。
So cold cuts are meats that you serve cold normally.
所以冷切肉通常是冷吃的肉类。
They're usually cured.
它们通常是腌制的。
They're not like raw pork or raw beef.
它们不像生猪肉或生牛肉那样。
You put them on a sandwich.
你把他们放在三明治上。
So cured meats would be like that they're smoked.
所以腌制肉就是那种烟熏过的。
They're not cooked.
它们不是煮熟的。
No they're not cooked.
不，它们不是煮熟的。
You're right.
你说得对。
They're smoked or they're cured with a kind of chemical or brine.
它们是烟熏的，或者用某种化学物质或盐水腌制的。
That means that they're preserved.
这意味着它们被保存了。
They can last for a long time.
它们可以保存很长时间。
Alright very good.
好的，非常好。
So that's what we're getting at the deli.
这就是我们要在熟食店买的东西。
Usually at the deli you can pick up meats, cheeses, and pickles and all that.
通常在熟食店你可以买到肉、奶酪、泡菜等等。
All that good stuff.
所有那些好东西。
Alright so why don't we jump into our dialogue and listen to it for the first time.
好的，那我们为什么不直接进入对话，第一次听一下呢。
Honey we're all out of wine and cheese.
亲爱的，我们的葡萄酒和奶酪都吃完了。
Do you mind running to the deli and picking up a few things?
你介意去趟熟食店买点东西吗？
Can it wait?
能等会儿吗？
I'm watching the game right now.
我正在看比赛呢。
Your friends and family are coming over tonight and we still need to get a lot of things.
你的朋友和家人今晚要来，我们还有很多东西要准备。
Fine.
好吧。
What do you need?
你需要什么？
Okay pick up some cured meats to go with the wine.
好的，买些腌制肉来配葡萄酒。
Maybe a pound of Polish sausages, ham, liverwurst, salami, and any other cold cuts that are on
大概一磅波兰香肠、火腿、肝肠、萨拉米香肠，还有任何其他特价的
sale.
冷切肉。
I think I saw a promotion for pastrami.
我想我看到五香熏牛肉有促销。
Also get some coleslaw and a jar of olives.
再买些凉拌卷心菜和一罐橄榄。
Whoa wait a minute.
哇，等一下。
Isn't that a bit too much?
是不是有点太多了？
I mean how much is all this going to cost?
我是说这些总共要花多少钱？
Never mind that.
别管那个了。
Get some dips as well.
再买些蘸酱。
Get a jar of spinach and blue cheese dips and also some tzatziki.
买一罐菠菜和蓝纹奶酪蘸酱，再来些希腊酸奶黄瓜酱。
If they have bean dip, get that as well.
如果他们有豆泥，也买点。
Last but not least, get some pickles.
最后但同样重要的是，买些泡菜。
Is that all your majesty?
就这些吗，陛下？
Very funny.
真会开玩笑。
Get a move on.
快点行动吧。
People will be here any minute.
人们随时都会到。
Alright we're back.
好的，我们回来了。
So now we're going to go into language takeaway where we're going to take a look at six key
现在我们要进入语言要点环节，看看六个关键
words.
词汇。
Language takeaway.
语言要点。
Alright so the first key word that we have, we actually talked about it already but just
好的，我们第一个关键词，其实我们已经聊过了，但只是
to make sure that you got it.
为了确保你明白了。
Those are cured meats.
那就是腌制肉。
Cured meats.
腌制肉。
Well, to cure something is to preserve it in this case.
嗯，腌制在这里就是保存的意思。
So be careful because to cure has a couple of different meanings but when we're talking
所以要小心，因为“cure”有几个不同的意思，但当我们谈论
about food, something that is cured is preserved.
食物时，腌制的就是被保存的。
For example, pickles are cured in salty water.
例如，泡菜是在盐水里腌制的。
Brine.
盐水。
Oh is that what it's called?
哦，是这么叫的吗？
Brine?
盐水？
Salty water.
咸水。
I don't know what pickles are.
我不知道泡菜是什么。
But pickles are like, if you don't put them in brine, they don't taste all soury and nasty.
但泡菜就像，如果你不把它们放在盐水里，它们就不会有那种酸酸的味道。
No, that's because they're cucumbers.
不，那是因为它们是黄瓜。
So a cucumber becomes a pickle after it's been cured.
所以黄瓜经过腌制后就变成了泡菜。
So we could talk about pork but when pork is cured, it becomes ham.
所以我们可以聊猪肉，但猪肉经过腌制后就成了火腿。
Okay.
好的。
Awesome.
太棒了。
So cured meats are meats that have been preserved through some kind of process like using salt
所以腌制肉类就是通过某种过程（比如用盐）保存的肉，
or drying them.
或者风干它们。
Okay.
好的。
Awesome.
太棒了。
So a cured meat, I think maybe is liverwurst.
所以一种腌制肉类，我觉得可能是肝肠。
Okay.
好的。
Well, this is a German lesson now, not just an English lesson.
嗯，这现在变成德语课了，不只是英语课。
In English, we have a lot of words that come from German and one of these words is wurst.
在英语里，我们有很多来自德语的词，其中一个就是“wurst”。
Okay.
好的。
And that means sausage, right?
那意思是香肠，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
Sausage.
香肠。
So bratwurst, liverwurst.
所以有德式香肠、肝肠。
And in this case, liverwurst, I'm sure you can guess what part of the pig that comes
而在这个例子中，肝肠，我敢肯定你能猜到它来自猪的哪个部位，
from.
来自。
Liver.
肝脏。
Very good, Marco.
非常好，马可。
You get a star for the day.
你今天得一颗星。
Awesome.
太棒了。
Yeah.
是的。
No.
不。
Liverwurst is a kind of sausage that's made up of this part of the animal.
肝肠是一种用动物这个部位制成的香肠。
Okay.
好的。
Actually, I've never, I don't know if I've had liverwurst.
实际上，我从来没吃过，我不知道我有没有吃过肝肠。
What does it look like?
它长什么样？
Is it white?
是白色的吗？
Is it red?
是红色的吗？
Is it dark?
是深色的吗？
I think it's like light, purplish, whitish.
我觉得它像是浅色、带点紫色、带点白色。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I've had bloodwurst.
我吃过血肠。
That's good.
那很好吃。
Yeah.
是的。
Blood sausage is delicious.
血肠很美味。
Okay.
好的。
And well, apart from picking up meats and cheeses at the deli, you can also pick up
嗯，除了在熟食店买肉和奶酪，你还可以买
coleslaw.
凉拌卷心菜。
All right.
好的。
Coleslaw is an American classic.
凉拌卷心菜是美式经典。
I'm sure you could get this other places as well, though.
不过我相信你在其他地方也能买到。
It's basically a cold salad that's made up of cabbage and carrots and maybe onions.
它基本上是一种冷沙拉，由卷心菜、胡萝卜，可能还有洋葱做成。
But generally, the sauce is white.
但通常，酱汁是白色的。
It's like a mayonnaise and vinegar sauce.
它是一种蛋黄酱和醋的酱汁。
So it's very stringy, lots of thin, long pieces and the sauce is white.
所以它很细长，有很多细长的条，酱汁是白色的。
Okay.
好的。
Yeah.
是的。
I think this is a very American thing.
我觉得这很美国化。
I'm not really sure if I've seen coleslaw in many other places, but I personally don't
我不太确定我是否在其他地方见过凉拌卷心菜，但我个人不喜欢它。
like it.
不喜欢。
Again, because of the whole vinegar thing.
还是因为醋的问题。
I'm not a big fan of the bitter stuff.
我不太喜欢苦的东西。
Yeah.
是的。
I love, we also call it slaw, sometimes with a side of slaw.
我喜欢，我们也叫它“slaw”，有时配上一份 slaw。
I love a hot dog with a side of coleslaw.
我喜欢热狗配上一份凉拌卷心菜。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
My favorite meals.
我最喜欢的餐点之一。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
Okay.
好的。
So coleslaw.
所以凉拌卷心菜。
Moving on, we have an interesting sauce.
继续，我们有一种有趣的酱汁。
It's Greek, I believe.
我觉得是希腊的。
That is correct.
没错。
And I'm not going to try to pronounce it because I might mess it up.
我不打算试着发音，因为我可能会搞砸。
So I'm going to leave that one to you.
所以我把这个留给你。
Well, I don't speak Greek, but this is how we say it in America.
嗯，我不会说希腊语，但这是我们在美国怎么说的。
Tzatziki.
酸奶黄瓜酱。
Okay.
好的。
Tzatziki is a food that comes from Greece, like you said.
酸奶黄瓜酱是一种来自希腊的食物，就像你说的。
In America, we have a lot of different foods, in Europe too, wherever.
在美国，我们有很多不同的食物，在欧洲也是，无论哪里。
People come from all over the place.
人们来自世界各地。
And in America, we've adopted a number of foods.
在美国，我们采纳了很多食物。
One of these foods is tzatziki.
其中一种就是酸奶黄瓜酱。
It's a white yogurt dip.
它是一种白色的酸奶蘸酱。
Okay.
好的。
So usually in tzatziki, there is some onion, some cucumber, some pepper, but it's a really
所以通常酸奶黄瓜酱里有一些洋葱、一些黄瓜、一些辣椒，但它是一种非常
good thick, creamy yogurt dip that you use with bread or chips.
一种浓稠、奶油状的酸奶蘸酱，用来配面包或薯片吃。
Okay.
好的。
And that's actually our next word.
这其实是我们下一个单词。
You mentioned it's a dip.
你提到了它是一种蘸酱。
So you're using that as a noun and that's our next word, dip.
所以你把那个词当名词用，这就是我们下一个单词，dip。
Dip.
Dip。
So basically, a dip is a kind of food that you eat with other foods.
基本上，dip 是一种和其他食物一起吃的食物。
Okay.
好的。
So it's like a sauce.
所以它有点像酱料。
Exactly.
没错。
It's a sauce for finger foods.
它是一种手指食物的酱料。
So basically, a dip is a food you eat with other foods.
所以基本上，dip 是一种和其他食物一起吃的食物。
So you can have chips and dip.
所以你可以有薯片和蘸酱。
That would be potato chips with dip.
那就是薯片配蘸酱。
And sometimes you have tomato dip or cheese dip.
有时候还有番茄蘸酱或奶酪蘸酱。
In this case, we have tzatziki or blue cheese dip.
在这个例子里，我们有 tzatziki 或蓝纹奶酪蘸酱。
Blue cheese dip.
蓝纹奶酪蘸酱。
But actually, it's also a verb, right?
但实际上，它也是个动词，对吧？
To dip.
蘸。
So when you take your potato chip and you dip it in the dip.
所以当你拿起薯片，把它蘸进蘸酱里。
You can say that.
你可以这么说。
Yes.
是的。
Dip it in the dip.
把它蘸进蘸酱里。
Okay.
好的。
So you dip your potato chip in the dip.
所以你把薯片蘸进蘸酱里。
Yes.
是的。
Very good.
非常好。
So those are all the words that we have for you today on Language Takeaway.
这些就是今天“语言小课堂”为你准备的所有单词。
Why don't we go back, listen to the dialogue again, and we'll be back in a bit with Fluency
我们不如回去再听一遍对话，稍后回来继续“流利度
Builder.
提升”环节。
Honey, we're all out of wine and cheese.
亲爱的，我们的酒和奶酪都没了。
Do you mind running to the deli and picking up a few things?
你能跑一趟熟食店买点东西吗？
Can't wait.
等不及了。
I'm watching the game right now.
我正在看比赛呢。
Your friends and family are coming over tonight, and we still need to get a lot of things.
你的朋友和家人今晚要来，我们还有很多东西要准备。
Fine.
好吧。
What do you need?
你需要什么？
Okay.
好的。
Pick up some cured meats to go with the wine.
买些腌肉来配酒。
Maybe a pound of Polish sausages, ham, liverwurst, salami, and any other cold cuts that are on
可能来一磅波兰香肠、火腿、肝肠、萨拉米，还有任何其他在
sale.
打折的冷切肉。
I think I saw a promotion for pastrami.
我好像看到熏牛肉有促销。
Also, get some coleslaw and a jar of olives.
还有，买点凉拌卷心菜和一罐橄榄。
Whoa, wait a minute.
哇，等一下。
Isn't that a bit too much?
这会不会太多了？
I mean, how much is all this going to cost?
我是说，这些总共要花多少钱？
Never mind that.
别管那个了。
Get some dips as well.
再买些蘸酱。
Get a jar of spinach and blue cheese dips and also some tzatziki.
买一罐菠菜蘸酱、蓝纹奶酪蘸酱，还有一些 tzatziki。
If they have bean dip, get that as well.
如果有豆泥蘸酱，也买点。
Last but not least, get some pickles.
最后但同样重要的是，买些泡菜。
Is that all, Your Majesty?
就这些了吗，陛下？
Very funny.
真会开玩笑。
Get a move on.
快点行动吧。
People will be here any minute.
人们随时会到。
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
Now let's take a look at three key phrases on Fluency Builder.
现在来看看“流利度提升”中的三个关键短语。
Fluency Builder.
流利度提升。
This first one is a very, very common phrase.
第一个是一个非常非常常见的短语。
We use this a lot in English when we're maybe running late or you need something very quickly.
在英语中，当我们可能快迟到了或需要很快拿到某样东西时，经常用这个。
We say, hey, can you run to the store and get this?
我们会说，嘿，你能跑趟商店买这个吗？
Or do you mind running to the deli?
或者你介意跑一趟熟食店吗？
So the verb here is to run to.
所以这里的动词是 run to。
Run to.
Run to。
Run to the deli.
跑到熟食店。
Does this mean that you're actually going to walk very fast to the deli?
这是说你真的要快步走到熟食店吗？
You're going to run?
你要跑吗？
No, this is not literal.
不，这不是字面意思。
This is not, okay, I'm going to go to the deli and I'm going to get some food.
这不是说，好的，我要去熟食店，然后买些食物。
No, this is going quickly.
不，这是指快速去。
So I could say, Marco, I have no time.
所以我可以这么说，Marco，我没时间了。
Can you run to the store and get me some milk, please?
你能跑趟商店帮我买点牛奶吗？
Okay, so that means just go really quickly in your car, your motorcycle, any way you
好的，所以意思就是快速去，开车、骑摩托车，任何方式
can.
都行。
Or walking, yeah, exactly.
或者走路，对，没错。
Good.
好的。
So that's run to the store, run to the deli.
所以这就是 run to the store，run to the deli。
In this case, we saw it in the sentence, do you mind running to the deli?
在这个例子里，我们在句子中看到的是 do you mind running to the deli？
So do you mind going quickly?
所以就是“你介意快速去一趟吗？”
So this is going quickly.
所以这是指快速去。
Do you mind running to the deli?
你介意跑一趟熟食店吗？
This is a thing that we can do.
这是我们可以做的事情。
And so she was telling him what to get and he's like, whoa, this is going to be really
于是她告诉他该买什么，他心想，哇，这得花不少钱啊。
expensive.
贵。
And she answered with this phrase, never mind that.
她用这句话回答：别管那个。
Never mind that.
别管那个。
Okay, this is a phrase that we use when we want to say, don't worry about it.
好的，这是一个短语，当我们想说“别担心”时使用。
That doesn't matter.
那不重要。
No problem.
没问题。
It's not important.
这不重要。
So, never mind, you could say by itself, never mind, forget about it.
所以，“never mind”可以单独说，意思是“算了，忘了吧”。
But never mind that is like saying, this argument is over, it's not a problem.
但“never mind that”就像在说：这个话题结束了，没问题。
So never mind that.
所以别管那个。
As I was saying, let's go to the store.
就像我刚才说的，我们去商店吧。
Okay, good.
好的，不错。
So it's not important, it's not relevant, don't worry about it.
所以这不重要，不相关，别担心。
Very good.
非常好。
And the last phrase that we have for you is a very interesting phrase when the girl said,
我们为你准备的最后一个短语很有趣，当女孩说：
you know what, very funny, but get a move on.
你知道吗，真搞笑，但赶紧动身吧。
People will be here any minute.
人们随时会到。
Get a move on.
赶紧动身。
So as we often say here at EnglishPod, this is the kind of phrase we have to look at as
所以，就像我们在EnglishPod常说的，这种短语我们要把它看作：
a chunk, as a unit, as one piece.
一个整体，一个单位，一个片段。
You can say get, get me this, or I move, I moved my house.
你可以说“get”、“get me this”，或者“I move”、“I moved my house”。
But get a move on means hurry up.
但“get a move on”意思是快点。
Start leaving now.
现在出发。
Go, go to the store, be quick about it.
去，去商店，快点。
So this is a command.
所以这是一个命令。
Get a move on.
赶紧动身。
Okay, so take it as a phrase, just like you know the phrase hurry up or go quickly.
好的，把它当作一个短语，就像你知道的“hurry up”或“go quickly”。
Remember the phrase get a move on as a way of saying, come on, quickly, go, go, go, quickly.
记住“get a move on”这个短语，意思是：快点，赶紧，走，走，走，快点。
That's right.
没错。
Or as I always say when I'm with friends and we're going slowly somewhere, I say, hey,
或者，当我和朋友在一起，我们走得很慢时，我常说：嘿，
guys, let's get a move on.
伙计们，我们赶紧动身吧。
Let's get a move on.
我们赶紧动身。
They're going to close.
他们要关门了。
Let's get going.
我们走吧。
Let's go here.
我们走这边。
Okay, very good.
好的，非常好。
So get a move on.
所以“get a move on”。
Get a move on and why don't we go back and listen to the dialogue for one last time.
“get a move on”，我们为什么不回去再听一遍对话呢？
Honey, we're all out of wine and cheese.
亲爱的，我们的酒和奶酪都吃完了。
Do you mind running to the deli and picking up a few things?
你介意跑一趟熟食店买点东西吗？
Can it wait?
能等会儿吗？
I'm watching the game right now.
我正在看比赛。
Your friends and family are coming over tonight and we still need to get a lot of things.
你的朋友和家人今晚要来，我们还有很多东西要准备。
Fine.
好吧。
What do you need?
你需要什么？
Okay, pick up some cured meats to go with the wine.
好的，买点腌肉配酒。
Maybe a pound of Polish sausages, ham, liverwurst, salami and any other cold cuts that are on
大概一磅波兰香肠、火腿、肝肠、萨拉米，还有任何打折的冷切肉。
sale.
打折的。
I think I saw a promotion for pastrami.
我记得看到五香熏牛肉有促销。
Also, get some coleslaw and a jar of olives.
还有，买点凉拌卷心菜和一罐橄榄。
Whoa, wait a minute.
哇，等一下。
Isn't that a bit too much?
这会不会太多了？
I mean, how much is all this going to cost?
我是说，这些总共要花多少钱？
Never mind that.
别管那个。
Get some dips as well.
再买点蘸酱。
Get a jar of spinach and blue cheese dips and also some tzatziki.
买一罐菠菜蓝纹奶酪蘸酱，还有一些酸奶黄瓜酱。
If they have bean dip, get that as well.
如果有豆酱，也买点。
Last but not least, get some pickles.
最后但同样重要的是，买点泡菜。
Is that all, your majesty?
就这些了吗，陛下？
Very funny.
真搞笑。
Get a move on.
赶紧动身。
People will be here any minute.
人们随时会到。
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So now, Catherine, I understand you're a big fan of pickles and olives and all that stuff.
那么现在，凯瑟琳，我知道你很喜欢泡菜、橄榄之类的东西。
I love cured food.
我喜欢腌制的食物。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
Pickled.
腌制的。
Have you ever had a pickled tomato?
你吃过腌番茄吗？
I hate pickled tomatoes.
我讨厌腌番茄。
Pickled tomatoes, pickled pickles, pickled olives, everything.
腌番茄、腌泡菜、腌橄榄，所有东西。
I love it all.
我都喜欢。
I hate, I actually, there are a couple of things that I don't really like.
我讨厌，实际上，有几样东西我不太喜欢。
For example, coleslaw, you mentioned that it has cabbage in it and many people may know
比如，凉拌卷心菜，你提到里面有卷心菜，很多人可能知道
this vegetable as this purple lettuce, right?
这种蔬菜是这种紫色的生菜，对吧？
It looks like a lettuce, but it's purple.
它看起来像生菜，但它是紫色的。
That's right.
没错。
I hate it.
我讨厌它。
I don't like it.
我不喜欢它。
And I actually hate olives and pickles.
而且我其实讨厌橄榄和腌黄瓜。
I can't really eat them.
我真的吃不了它们。
Sounds like you don't like bitter things like vinegar, olives.
听起来你不喜欢苦的东西，比如醋、橄榄。
Yeah, yeah, no.
对，对，不。
Not a big fan.
不太喜欢。
I'm not a big fan of anything that's bitter.
我不太喜欢任何苦的东西。
I love it.
我喜欢它。
It's one of my favorite.
它是我最喜欢的之一。
I love salty foods and I love bitter foods and that's all I have to say about it.
我喜欢咸的食物，也喜欢苦的食物，这就是我要说的。
I've never really understood how people have like a whole pickle and they take it out of
我一直不明白人们怎么拿一整根腌黄瓜，从罐子里拿出来，
the jar and they just bite into it.
然后直接咬下去。
It's like, that's nasty.
感觉就是，真恶心。
Well, the adjective to describe a pickle's flavor is sour.
嗯，用来形容腌黄瓜味道的形容词是酸。
Sour.
酸。
It's very sour.
它很酸。
And in America, at delis, you can buy full sours or half sours.
在美国，熟食店里你可以买到全酸或半酸的腌黄瓜。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
Some pickles are less sour than others.
有些腌黄瓜比其他酸度低一些。
We call it a half sour.
我们叫它半酸。
My favorite pickles are full sours.
我最喜欢的腌黄瓜是全酸的。
Really?
真的吗？
Make you cry a little bit.
会让你有点想哭。
The whole pickle thing, is this very American?
整个腌黄瓜这件事，是很美国化的吗？
Because you always have pickles in burgers, for example, right?
因为比如在汉堡里，你总是有腌黄瓜，对吧？
You go to McDonald's, you have pickles in burgers.
你去麦当劳，汉堡里就有腌黄瓜。
Is this very American or is this coming from another place?
这是很美国化的，还是从别的地方传来的？
It comes from Europe.
它来自欧洲。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
A lot of German food involves pickles, pickled vegetables.
很多德国菜都涉及腌黄瓜、腌蔬菜。
The Koreans also, Korean food has a lot of pickled vegetables like kimchi, which is pickled
韩国人也一样，韩国菜有很多腌蔬菜，比如泡菜，那是腌制的
cabbage.
白菜。
Oh, that's right.
哦，没错。
And in Chinese culture as well, a lot of pickled foods.
在中国文化中，也有很多腌制食品。
So I think this is something that's very common all over the world.
所以我认为这是全世界都很常见的东西。
You can have pickled fish.
你可以有腌鱼。
Really?
真的吗？
Yeah.
是的。
You can pickle anything.
什么都可以腌。
I don't know if we pickle things in Latin America.
我不知道拉丁美洲我们是否腌制东西。
This is why it seems very strange to me.
这就是为什么它对我来说很陌生。
But this is a really interesting topic.
但这真是一个有趣的话题。
Why don't you let us know what your favorite cured meats are?
为什么不告诉我们你最喜欢的腌制肉类是什么？
I know there are a lot of different types.
我知道有很多不同的种类。
And if you like pickles or not, maybe some people out there will support me and say they
还有你是否喜欢腌黄瓜，也许有些人会支持我，说他们
don't like pickles.
不喜欢腌黄瓜。
All right.
好的。
And if you have delis in your home country, let us know.
如果你的国家有熟食店，告诉我们。
I've always been curious about this.
我一直对此很好奇。
Do you have delis or do you just have a butcher shop?
你们有熟食店，还是只有肉铺？
What's the difference?
有什么区别？
Awesome.
太棒了。
So we'll see everyone there, EnglishPod.com.
那我们就在那里见，EnglishPod.com。
Until next time.
下次再见。
Bye everyone.
大家再见。
Have a great day.
祝你有美好的一天。